{
    "subject": "resource/Ben_Tackie",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Accra",
    "human_readable": "Ben Tackie was born in Accra.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8637920618057251,
            "question": "Where was Ben Tackie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8069747090339661,
            "question": "When was Ben Tackie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2824617922306061,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Ben Tackie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27561870217323303,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Accra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24518728256225586,
            "question": "What is Accra known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2272968888282776,
            "question": "What is life like in Accra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17965054512023926,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Accra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11086743324995041,
            "question": "What is the significance of Accra in Ghanaian culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0975911095738411,
            "question": "What country is Accra the capital of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04467891901731491,
            "question": "Who are some notable individuals from Ghana?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ben Tackie was born in Accra.",
            "html": "dbpedia_484_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Accra the capital of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_484_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Accra in Ghanaian culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_484_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the history of Accra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_484_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_484_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, there are multiple mentions of Ben Tackie's birthplace as Accra, Ghana. The earliest mention is in the first document, where it says \"Benjamin Tackie, (born 1973-07-23 in Accra, Ghana)...\". This information is consistent throughout all the other documents, including the one that lists his birthdate and nationality. Therefore, the triple \"Ben Tackie was born in Accra\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that both \"48.txt\" and \"30.txt\" indicate Ben Tackie was born in Accra, Ghana."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}